[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city, nicknamed The Mile-High City, is located on the plains east of the Rocky Mountains?", "correct_answer": "Denver, Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Aurora, Colorado", "Aspen, Colorado", "Phoenix, Arizona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the Drama Club teacher, portrayed by Alyson Reed in the movie High School Musical?", "correct_answer": "Ms. Darbus", "incorrect_answers": ["Ms. Smith", "Ms. Ryan", "Ms. Danforth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "German astronomer Johannes Kepler showed that the planets circle the Sun in this type of path.", "correct_answer": "Ellipse", "incorrect_answers": ["Ray", "Circle", "Hyperbola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog, whose name means barker in Russian, became the first living creature from Earth to enter orbit.", "correct_answer": "Laika", "incorrect_answers": ["Mandy", "Lucky", "Sporty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which goofy Star Wars character turned into a well spoken senator?", "correct_answer": "Jar Jar Binks", "incorrect_answers": ["Bail Organa", "Nute Gunray", "Padme Amidala"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A popular method of finding a vampires grave involved this animal that would supposedly balk at the grave.", "correct_answer": "Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken", "Black cat", "Wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed Traffic, Oceans11 and Erin Brockovich?", "correct_answer": "Steve Soderbergh", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Greengrass", "George Clooney", "Don Siegel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state sport of Maryland?", "correct_answer": "Jousting", "incorrect_answers": ["Steeplechase", "Lacrosse", "Horse racing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This world-famous manufacturer of athletic shoes has its origins in a company called Blue Ribbon Sports, founded by Phil Knight and his track coach, Bill Bowerman.", "correct_answer": "Nike", "incorrect_answers": ["Adidas", "K-Swiss", "Reebok"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1988 drama movie, starring Meryl Streep, follows the real-life case of Azaria Chamberlain, a baby who disappeared in 1980.", "correct_answer": "A Cry in the Dark", "incorrect_answers": ["A Child in the Storm", "A Tear in the Silence", "A Soul in the Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was The Blair Witch Project released?", "correct_answer": "1999", "incorrect_answers": ["2002", "1997", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the longest continuous stretch of railroad.", "correct_answer": "Trans-Siberian Railroad", "incorrect_answers": ["The Orient Express", "The Canadian Pacific Railroad", "The Alaska-Canadian Railroad"]}]